(Speed Clock)
I want to climb the mountain
I choose swimming-pool
I like to go to seaside
I like to take a nap
Take a nap?
As if it's Nobita's work-style
Summer vacation will come in three days
I'm waiting for it urgently
I hope summer vacation will come quickly
The day and night will pass quickly
The three days will be over at once
Is it three hours?
It's only ten minutes
after you came back from school
Time runs too slow
Doraemon, has an hour passed
It's only three minutes,
you're long-winded
Ah, it's too slow
I worry about it too much
Doraemon,
be quick to think an idea out
I almost can't wait for it any longer
I have a way
Sorry to trouble you
Doraemon, is it OK
I don't like this method
It's speed clock
The poiner will be made a round
The sun goes under
It's dark
Make a round again,
the moon goes under again
The sun rises again
It'll be tomorrow
Great, Doraemon
Make rounds any more
It's summer vacation
after you make two rounds
Summer vacation came already
I don't believe that
Great,
I think I've to wait for three days
It's so quick
This is my exploit
Really
Yeah
I have this clock
You may request me
if you want to use it
Nobita, you're great
Let's go to the swimming-pool to play
It's too lovely
Nobita,
is it OK that you play all the time
Be quick to do your homework
or you'll worry about it
I know
Damn
It's a fine day today
I want to sleep unknowingly
Nobita
Did you do your homework
Did you do your homework on earth
Why don't you obey me
Take occasion to finish your homework
Ah?
It's late already, I'll do it tomorrow
It's strange...
What will I play
OK, I'll go to catch hexapod
I almost can't wait for tomorrow
Change now to tomorrow
You'll waste much time in this way
I know
It's bright now, I'll go out
I must catch hexapod today
Return it to me, this is my hexapod
Cheapskate, lend it to me
I'll return it to you tomorrow
Damn...
Nobita, let tomorrow come quickly
OK
Move, move, move
Jian
It's tomorrow already
Return it to me
Be quick
Shizuka
Ah?
Ah, it's raining
It's rare that
we want to go to the swimming-pool
It's raining really
The weather forecasted
the rain would stop tomorrow
Must it be tomorrow
I have an idea
It's too shining
Nobita,
let's go to the swimming-pool quickly
Let's go
My petunias doesn't flower at all time
I can't write the observation diary
It's terrible
I want to see the petunias to flower
Be quick to turn the clock
Nix! It made speed many days
Damn, you dare to refuse me
I'll do it
The petunias flower
The petunias flower...
Here you are, this is present
Doraemon, thank you,
I'm too happy
But can you finish your homework
in a day
A day? Homework?
It's only a day
Terrible! Terrible!
So I'm right
Nobita
Your homework haven't been done
How to do
So I said that
Doraemon, think a way out quickly
Use the speed clock to turn it back
So I said that
Return to the original state
I'm saved!
I feel it's summer vacation
but there're still two days
I can't wait
Great
(Girlfriend List)
Make yourself
Of course
You may try your best to eat
Sure
What will we do for you
About this thing
Do you know Dachangliumeizi
of the class next to us
Yes, I heard she's the most beautiful
in our school
I want to marry her when I grow up
Do you want to marry her
It's too funny
It's too early for you to think it now
You're only a pupil, it's too strange
It's you who don't know the condition!
Many men want to make friends with her
Now, it's the best chance
It'll be too late when I grow up
It's bad if you haven't plan
So I want to make the chance
to let her know
I'm an excellent youngster
Must you have plan in your life
That guy is very clever
I ought to begin to think about it
Ought I to seek her
Nobita like the cake very much
Why don't you eat it?
I'm full now
If I'd known I might have the cake,
I'd not have so much
Nobita, may I have it
Of course
I'd not eat popcorns, if I'd known
I could have the cake
This is an important problem
It's not only canapes' problem
but also it's life's...
Doraemon, come here,
do me a favour
I want to know all girls
who'll be around me
before I'm 25 years old
Do you have that scene
It's difficult to realize your request
Girlfriends list making machine
will list the ladies' photographs
who you'll know
But what do you want to do
This is a secret
In fact...
But didn't you see Shizuka
with the machine
But the future will change
Wedding is the most important thing
If the delicious cake appears
it'll be pity
I don't know who'll be my girlfriend
I'm too tense
She appeared!
I love the two girls
Shiyuanyujiaflg
she's my middle school classmate
Siyezhenzhizi
she's my colleague
Nobita
Shizuka's coming
Please wait a moment
Yeah
Nobita
It's strange, she's here just now
Sorry, Shizuka, I'm busy now
I'd better know the two girls more now
What a big house
The piano sound can be heard
Whenever, Beethoven's
melodies are so nice
This is Tchaikovshy's melody
I love that man named Tchaikovshy
Who are you
Where did you come in from
That...
Mum
See you
It's dangerous, can't I be remembered
ls Shiyuan's home this way
You must be careful this time
I don't know which room is it
Who are you
lam... that...
Say it clearly
What's the matter, grandpa?
Are you Nobita
Do you know me?
You're the student in the nearby
school,but I always hear you
Am I so famous
You're always late
and you're reprimanded by your teacher
Sorry to trouble you
to make a good renown for me
I beg you! I beg you!
You're too shameless
Don't you know what you are
You're foolish and bad-looking
what's more, you're not good at sport
Do you have qualification
If someone want to be married to you
you ought to be quick to marry her
thankfully
Sorry, I ought not to be a playboy
Please pardon me, Shizuka
What's the matter with you, Nobita
( Pocket Telescope)
The dog's walking
Right, great
Return the yoyo to me
I'll keep it
Nobody can be so
Never mind,
in either case you're not good at yoyo
Jian plays yoyo, it's yoyo's happiness
Good
I'll give you it
after I'm tired of playing
How can it be so
You're so useless
You may glom the yoyo back by yourself
If I can do that
I'll not cry
Damn, you're too useless
Pocket telescope
What's this
It may take stuffs from far away
For example
Gong cake
It's so
Delicious
Yeah, horrify him
If you can catch the stuff
you may offer your hand
MY Shopping basket
It disappeared!
Are you looking for this?
It's strange that it appeared again
OK, I'll get it if it's so
You may practice first
What will you get
A wildcat
OK
I caught it wrong
Sorry, pardon me
You ought to aim at it well, Nobita
I found it, Ok, move
It disappeared
Help me, I did it wrong again
I caught the branch,
but I was pulled back
If you're back,
you'll catch it this way
Right, no problem
OK
I'll make Shizuka surprise
I found it
Shizuka
Nobita, when did you come here
Sorry, I'm looking for Jian, Bye
Bye
Damn
Good, the eyesight is the widest here
No, no, it's too dirty
It'll be OK there
It's good here
We're playing sparetime baseball
A good pitch
It's too quick, it can't be hit
Good
Hah!
Come on
I succeed! I succeed!
It's very funny
Well, where's Jian
Thief
Hey
Stop! Stop!
Help me
No way, you can't escape
Mr. Police, help me please
The genie appeared
You're too strange,
go to the police office
As if it became golly
Jian
I found it at last
Aim at it carefully
I succeed! I got it!
It's strange...
Hey, where's the yoyo
I don't know, maybe it's nearby
Then you'll look for it quickly
They horrified me
It's a reckoning to you
Play a joke again
Er...
What a pain! What did you do!
What? You said what I've done?
Nothing
OK, once more please
l succeed
Ah?
Damn, this guy
I don't know
Nonsense, It must be you
Stand there! Suneo! Don't run
I may have a rest
Well, return the cloths to Jian
Hey, the kiddy
It's very dangerous there,
come down quickly
Terrible, I must be back quickly
Ah? He disappeared?
Great, Nobita, I took it back
It may be the common telescope
The stars are very beautiful
It seems that I can touch them...
Nobody can pick star off
I never thought I can take it really
How to do? How to do?
(Home's further and further away)
Delicious
I had it already
Nix!
Nix, guttler
I gulped it
It's only a little
It doesn't need to care
No, it's dog pellet
What's the dog pellet
If you lose cat or dog
they can come back
If they eat it
they'll not be back
Why do you get the strange stuff out,
Doraemon?
I'm going to get it out to detrude
You must stay home
You'll not be back if you go out
Remember, you can't leave whatever
I know
OK, even the fire happen
I'll not go out
Nobita, can you help me
Let me help you at this time
You're not competent
Really, that's so
why do you so felonious
Nobita, come to my home to play
Shizuka, I want to go there,
but it's not OK now
Really, then It's next time
Damn, it's rare that Shizuka invite me,
but I can't go there
Nobita
A man's absent, you may join in it
What are you saying
I'll not be back if I go out now
It's rare that we invite you
We'll not invite you from now on
I want to go to play
It's the last ball
Terrible
Nix, I ate the dog pellet
Is it no problem if I don't go out
I left home negligently
But happily, I know the road
Go on this way
It doesn't matter, I can do that
It's too simple, no problem
Brother, excuse me
could you tell me how to walk
Sorry, I've no time, see you
Cool
I want to look for Shantian's home
What a trouble, now it's far away
Nobita went out
I told him not to
leave again and again
Terrible
Haven't you find him?
Are you a boob?
Don't make noise,
or it's hard to find the way
I'd better look for it by myself
Where's here
It's a new way
ls my home here
This way
Wait a moment
Is it that way
Is it this way?
It ought to be this way
May I ask you where my home is
Thank you
I was unhappy I told a lie just now
Wait a minute, I told you
the opposite direction just now
The opposite direction!
What's the matter
I lost myself
May I ask you
if you see this kiddy
He's there He's walking and crying
Thank you
What shall I do
Nobita
Doraemon
He ought to be here, it's strange
As if I heard Doraemon's voice
before I fell into the hole
Doraemon, help me quickly
May I ask you where my home is
What's the address?
I forgot it
Then I don't know
It seems that he'll be found
No dogs could return
after they ate the pellet
Can't I meet Nobita any longer
so long, Nobita
I'll remember you forever
Forever
I can't move
I'm too hungry
What is Dola A
Dream doing at this time
It seems that I become a dog
Delicious
Do you want to share with me,
thank you
I ate it
I thought it out
What a pain
Isn't it Nobita
I ate dogs' foods
I spat them out
so I'd be back
Great
I know the dogs' feeling well
Great Great
(Bribe War Plan)
Our Jian team is not good now
If it goes on, we'll fail this time
So I decided to assume
two armies system
The man whose grade's bad
will be weeded out
They'll not attend the match
What's more,
you may take the man who's good
so our team will be stronger
Disband
How can it be so... It's impossible
Isn't it? Won't you let him attend the
match because he's poor at the sport?
If it's so, he'll not progress forever
It means that
I'll not play baseball any longer
Jian minds the result too much
Sports ought not to be so
He has no qualification to be a coach
Nobita, I don't understand you
why do you think you'll be weeded out
Because... I'm the worst
You're wrong at this point
You know yourself
but why don't you work hard?
You must try your best to progress
to make yourself become the best man
Thank you, Doraemon
You're right
As if I felt sober
after I heard what you've said
That's OK that you can understand it
OK, I'll not stop exercising
until it's dark
Go!
Nix, the lesson is the more important
Mum will take care of this for a while
How can it be so
If it's so, I must be weeded out
I'll not play baseball for ever
No way
I guess the prop will be taken out
It's not good
Bribe bar
You take it to beg that man
maybe he'll not refuse you
Have a try
Mum, that...
I don't return you the baseball bar
This
What's this
You'd better take it
Really
Return me the baseball bar
and the jacketing
l succeed
Oh, what can I use it to do?
Don't think so much
Where do you peck it, Boob?
Sorry, I'll peck it well next time
Damn
What a pain
You're too boob
You look down upon me
It's the same
Run quickly! Quickly!
Or you'll be weeded out
You're too slow
Don't wigg me, damn
But you're too boob
Shut up, exit
I want to give up too
I hit it
It's me
Look, he's good
Great!
Can you be our guidance counselor
Sure
Then it'll be OK
Go back to prepare
the player beadroll at once
Remember,
It's me that I introduced the man
I know
I need to use it once again
Would you like another bribe bar?
No way, don't use it
for strange application
Take it
I know, this is the last time
It doesn't need to ask
I know
Give you this
What's this on earth
In a word, you take it
Really?
Of course, if you'll invite me
to attend the match of tomorrow
I see, this is men's appointment
I succeed
Nobita, wait a moment please
Sorry to take so nice stuff of yours
This is the receipt, take it
It doesn't matter
Nobita can understand me
It's impossible
I saw the team list
Why did Nobita take place of me
What's the matter
Don't ask so simple question
Of course Nobita's better than you
So you're weeded out...
Terrible
It's strange, because I'm
better than Nobita
Right, it's too unfair
Hey, I picked this
Receipt
Look, it's really strange
Jian, please explain it
I don't know
I don't know, really
Hey, Nobita, What's the boodle
What happened between you and Jian
Nobita can't be out because he's ill
It's impossible, let him come out
The thing's serious
Haven't you known
your mistake till now
What's the matter with Doraemon
If you don't have a try,
you'll not know it
Maybe I'll have a swat
I can't deny the possible
Wait to see, I must be excellent
Impossible
Jian, what's the matter
didn't the match stop
No, I'll play baseball
But it's raining
He took the boodle,
he must obey the appointment
However, I must let you play baseball
Try your best
Once again
Cheerio
It fits Nobita well
(We can't read in the Sahara)
Nobita, if you're egregious,
mum will not pardon you
You've time to talk nonsense,
why don't you read?
Why is mum angry?
Mum ordered me to read all the time
so I told her that
Do you know where Suneo's reading
His mother take a lease of a villa
in Qingjingze for a month
But look at your room
it's narrow and hot and dirty
I only want to tell her
if she wants to set me work hard
she must take a lease of a villa for me
You mean you'll study hard
if you have a good environment?
Right, I will
If we go to the Switzerland Park
but not Qingjingze
will you work harder?
The efficiency will be very high
I think I'll try my best to learn
If it's in the forest in Florida
or beside a lake of Canada
is it nice too?
I'll study from morning to evening
Where's here
The Gaspar Park in Canada
OK, be quick to work now
You machine
Sightseeing machine
Adjust the longitude and latitude
it'll transmit the scene there
It means this is the real
scene of Canada
The breeze is flowing
And the lake is shining, fantastic
The water is so cool
No, it's painful
It's the original room
Why not say this early
The stage has four stages
from the unit of 100km to 1 metre
It can be adjusted from far to near
So it can broadcast freely
from the North Pole to our home
Let me have a try
I want to broadcast the villa of Suneo
To direct against Japan like this
And reduce the scope
It's raining in Qingjingze
Mum, the rain is leaking here
No way, open this umbrella
Why did we borrow
this dilapidated frame house?
Because this is the cheapest
Oh! I see!
Lalala
HEY
Suneo, what's your feeling
How did you know
this is a secret
Try your best
Then Suneo'll be surprised
I saw it
What about other friends?
It's too hot
Look
Not only I suffer heatstroke...
I don't know how Shizuka is now
but also Shizuka
You always look at others, do you forget
my purpose of carrying the prop
Right, I almost forget it,
we'll work harder in a good entourage
Don't be angry
God will arrange me
Where's here
What a pain
It's nearby the Sahara
It's wide, attention will be dispersed
Then we've to look for other place
What's that
It seems that it's a man
Move the view to the northwest
about one kilometer
As if it's here
Go on straight
Someone died
Water... water...
Would you like water? OK
Here you are, this is water,I'm sorry
to keep you waiting for a longtime
It's bad, the true person's
in the faraway Sahara
Right
Since it's so
send ambulance to go there quickly
Now someone will die
It's in Sahara
at the right there...
How to do... how to do...
He'll die
Right, bring the convenience door out
Be quick
Where's the key?
I don't find it
Then we may use the carangid dragonfly
Use the carangid dragonfly...
No way
It'll spend too much time to go there
I'll die, I'll die
What a pity, I'll die here
You don't die now, don't say that
But nobody can save him
It's plane
This way, it's in this way
Someone is here
Great
He'll almost die
Really
Great What a surprise
Then decide the place where we read
No way, the view doesn't fit to read
You're finding fault
OK, let me find the view
It's impossible
You're wrong!
In either case it must be...
Be quick to read...
Nobita's teacher
I gave in you
(Cramm mirror)
I thought my face's like a cartoon
yesterday
I can't believe
I never thought I'm so good-looking
Maybe
I'm the most beautiful in the world
How to do... Right
You're the most beautiful in the world
The mirror said
I can show the truth
I only say the truth
No way, you make it cheat us
Doraemon, your mirror's interesting
No, it's cramm mirror
Cramm mirror?
You'd not better use it
He only caress you
Caress? Really?
No, you're wrong
That's the truth
I want to look into that mirror again
What's up?
Why do you play bowling at home
If you hurt, then how to do
It doesn't matter
Doraemon wasn't designed
It's a problem
Doraemon cam take another one out
It's that mirror
That's...
Don't be petty
But...
do you have mirror
Then you may get it out
But that...
Isn't it OK that I borrow it from you
Right!
I know
Is it me?
I'm so beautiful
Madam,
you're the most beautiful in the world
Really
If your hair's rippled into a bob,
it'll be better
Ripple it into a bob
I'll prepare at once
It's me this time
Mirror, mirror,
who's the most beautiful in the world
Of course it's you
Really?
It's strange, nobody said that to me
Because you're not marked
If your expression's revised,
you'll become better
Really?
Teach me quickly
It's too easy
It's the best
Now you'd better let others see
I used the gramary gumwater
to restore it in the end
How is it?
Why is it so?
That mirror said it's like a man
Stupid,
do you believe what the mirror said
Look, it's what you are
Impossible
I'm angry when I see it
Do you know it's powerful
I repaired it with difficult
Return the lie mirror to me
Nobita
Wait a moment, there's a mouse
Where's it? Where's it?
I only tell the truth forever
I'm the same with you
It's useless to let the men who have
no sense of beauty see it
Right
Doraemon can't appreciate
I'll let others see it
Well, I invite Shizuka to appreciate
Nobita's very charming
You must keep the expression
He's coming
Nobita
ls Shizuka here
She's playing volleyball
in the lung
Really, bye
What's the matter with his teeth?
Give you the mirror
Is it me?
I'm very charming
Right
If you listen to me,
you'll be the most beautiful
Tell me, tell me
What shall I do
OK, it's so...
Is it so?
Is it OK?
It's too pretty
I must invite others to have a look
Nobita
Shizuka
You're too rude, you'd not laugh
when you look at other's face
It's you
It's interesting
to look into the mirror alone
Me too
Goof
Nobita Shizuka
Strange, where has children gone
Guess
It's true
Everyone's the most attractive
Great
Hey, the lie mirror
You only talk nonsense
You're too hateful
Sorry, don't break me
Did you meditate
Yeah, I meditated
Mirror...
I want to look into the mirror...
It's mirror
Mirror
Who's the most beautiful in the world
This is your truth
It's too much
Weather you tell a lie or not,
the problem will come out
It's too much!
( Peck Rope )
ls Nobita in
I come to return the umbrella to you
Nobita
Doraemon, take it for me please
Take it by yourself
But you're near the door
No, no
Then I'll take it back
Is it OK?
He'll be back, quickly
I don't know how to deal with you
Peck rope
Take the umbrella back
What?
Ah?
What's that
Great
If you've the peck rope, you may take
stuff when you don't move
No way,
you always think some bad ideas out
I'll not lend it to you
Lend it to me, Doraemon
I lend it to Nobita each time,
but he doesn't use it well
I've an idea, you'd better get rid of it
It's the peck rope
If you don't want to have it,
I may take it
Then I can take stuffs from anywhere
OK, have a try
Take my neck
What a pain...
It's enough, I don't want to have it
I almost can't breathe
Great
Give me it I don't have it now
Quickly, I'll not use it at will
Lend it to me
Really?
Won't you use it to play tricks
I promise I won't
It's strange, it's not found
Impossible
I threw it out from the window just now
Terrible, it's taken
It's terrible if someone use it
to play monkey trick
Take it back!
Take back the cartoon book
what's reaved by Jian
Don't leak
What, what
What's the matter
It's true
Great, really
Brother, what's that
You said that too much
My notebook...
Shizuka finished her homework
I finished it
Thief, return it to me
I like this very much
I ate it
Don't run! Chief!
Damn, what's that strange rope
on earth
The ball...
It's too much
Who did it? I can't pardon him
Everyone's angry, how to do
I'm too angry
OK, let's look for the true criminal
It's bad... flee quickly
I found it
Great
Nobita, it's you
What're you saying
Don't be a fool,
you reaved our stuffs with it
I didn't do that
This is a common rope, bye
Damn, Jian caught up with us
Go home quickly
Nobita
As if the rope took my notebook away
That...
It came again
Terrible, all you doubt me
He ran away
He's not found
Damn, be quick to course
The man who took the rope away
plays gambade everywhere
Who's it on earth
Help!
Wait a moment, I'll use the peck rope
to help you at once
I'm practicing to peck rope
This is only common rope
I'll go back, see you
Look, it's Nobita
Really!
It's too egregious
It's that man
who played the rope just now
What?
I... It's not... me...
Don't run!
Nobita, happily
you didn't play monkey tricks
Thank you, brother
It's troublesome, I was kissed
Some faces are round
Some faces are long
Some faces are square
Some faces are triangular
Crying Angering Fawning and requesting
You'll become a ghost who likes crying
But if you smile
Your face will become round